[
    {
        "front": "れきし\n「歴史」",
        "back": "history",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "てら\n「寺」",
        "back": "temple",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "じんじゃ\n「神社」",
        "back": "shrine",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいぶつ\n「大仏」",
        "back": "large statue of the Buddha",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "せかい\n「世界」",
        "back": "world",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ざんねんな\n「残念な」",
        "back": "pity",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぜひ",
        "back": "definitely, by all means",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひじょうに\n「非常に」",
        "back": "really",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "めずらしい\n「珍しい」",
        "back": "rare",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうぶつ\n「動物」",
        "back": "animal",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "どうぶつえん\n「動物園」",
        "back": "zoo",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "うつくしい\n「美しい」",
        "back": "beautiful",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    },
    {
        "front": "たいけん（する）\n「体験」",
        "back": "experience / to experience",
        "chapter": "N4 C12"
    }
]